<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Explore | Digital Nomad]]></title>
  <link href="http://freespaceaniket.github.io/blog/categories/explore/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://freespaceaniket.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2016-05-20T15:01:36+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://freespaceaniket.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aniket Maithani]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[And It Started...]]></title>
    <link href="http://freespaceaniket.github.io/blog/2016/05/20/and-it-started-dot-dot-dot/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-20T15:00:25+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://freespaceaniket.github.io/blog/2016/05/20/and-it-started-dot-dot-dot</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It’s been quite a while since I’ve been on vacation and to be honest with the whole job shift and focusing on my coding skills last 6 months have been very hard for me. I came to know about my shortcomings which I was not able to recognize earlier probably because I was in my comfort zone. But skipping that part …. I was planning my trip since quite a while but something or the other pops up suddenly and I being a lazy ass as usual always dropped the plan.
So this Thursday [i.e on 12th of May] I suddenly decided to plan a OUT OF THE BOX trip to the hills. After arranging my financial stuff which I knew would last for at least couple of weeks if I plan to go out I was all in the mood to go. But other than that one of the key things that was bugging me was my office work since we are planning to launch our platform by the last week of this month. Fortunately, 90% of the work has been completed! so even the WORKING REMOTELY part will do.
Meanwhile on Friday I packed all of my stuff ran like a crazy horse to get my order of the day in line and by the 8 PM I was all set with my rucksack and other stuff which I was planning to carry for the trip. I booked the bus ticket to Shimla as I thought it would be a great starting point for my journey and furthermore I’ll be able to explore Himachal since I really haven’t seen much of the state.
I boarded the bus around 9:10 AM on Saturday and with my favorite tracks in my playlist buzzing in my ears I was in all mood… The journey was quite a tiresome one! as due to heavy traffic jams I reached Shimla around 7:30 PM. As I boarded off the bus A BAD NEWS STRIKE! the hotel which I booked using the MAKE MY TRIP website cancelled my booking and now I was in dire straits as with limited internet connectivity and this being a peak season I was looking for a new hotel to do my booking. BTW I haven’t complained about the refund etc. to MMT but for now I just don’t want to spoil my mood.
After taking direction for my hotel I reached the hotel around 9 PM and checked in! I was really tired and hungry since during the journey I am not a big fan of eating at any outlet! IDK if that’s a good thing or bad but I’ll leave for you guys to decide :P
After sorting out my luggage in the room I went out to check the mall road and to get something to eat also. I packed my food stuff and took a walk down the mall road and after capturing the few snaps I came back to my room.
It’s 5:30 AM on Sunday morning and I am planning to go out for a morning walk!</p>

<p>GOSH! I so love being close to the nature… Though Shimla comes in mainstream hill station but the kind of time I want with myself and nature .. this place is great for starters…..</p>

<p>So this is me signing off !!! Will update soon!
Adios!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
